啊…早知道就带驱虫剂来了
Arhhh, really wish I packed some insect propellent.
这次常规巡逻碰上的蚊子 个头都赶上吸血蝙蝠了
The mosquitoes out here on this routine recon are the size of vampire bats
而且吸血也不算少
and they drink just about as much of blood.
真是个野外生存专家啊 杰克
Quite the outdoorsman, aren't you, Jack?
你不会是在嘲笑我的求生包吧？
You wouldn't be making fun of my survival kit?
也许吧
Maybe.
我也许没有一身防叮咬的铁皮 阿尔茜
I may not have stinger-proof metal skin, Arcee
但在紧要关头 我可以用我的多功能军刀
but in a pinch, I can use my multi-function pocket knife
和镁棒打火石
and magnesium fire-starter
做一些速食奶酪通心粉
to cook up some freeze-dried mac and cheese.
你有你的办法 我有我的高招
You have your tools. I have mine.
有蹊跷
That's odd.
救护车的卫星扫描很准确
Ratchet's satellite scans were accurate
但地下能量矿不可能引起这种强烈感应
but subterranean energon deposits don't cause this kind of surge.
这是怎么回事？
What happened here?
飞船迫降
Crash landing.
待在我身后 小心跟紧
Stay behind me, low and close.
是汽车人 还是霸天虎？
Autobot or Decepticon?
说不准 在这里等着
Can't tell. Wait here.
阿…阿尔茜？
Ar... Arcee?
阿尔茜 出什么事了？
Arcee, what's wrong?
我知道这是谁的飞船了
I know who this ship belongs to.
阿尔茜呼叫基地 请尽快打开环陆桥
Arcee to base, I need a Ground Bridge ASAP.
等…等等 怎么了？
Wa... wait, why?
这是谁的飞船？
Whose ship is this?
基地 听到了吗？
Base, do you read?
见鬼！通讯链失灵了
Scrap! Comlink is dead.
这艘船肯定在发射高频干扰脉冲
The ship's got to be transmitting a high frequency scrambling pulse.
阿…阿尔茜？好吧 你吓着我了
Ar... Arcee? OK, you're kind of freaking me out here.
在这里等着
Wait here.
阿尔茜？
Arcee?
上车！
Climb on!
喔 阿尔茜？
Whoa, Arcee?
噢 好吧 至于这么紧张吗？
Ho, OK, was that really necessary?
阿尔茜呼叫基地…见鬼！
Arcee to base... scrap!
听着 危险我见得多了 这有什么大…
Look, I've seen danger before, what's the big...?
在这儿等着 我可不是开玩笑
Wait here, I mean it this time.
好吧 让我靠边就算了 现在又想甩了我？
OK, first you shut me out, now you're ditching me?
我以为我是你的搭档呢
I thought I was your partner.
不 杰克 你是个孩子！
No, Jack, you are a kid!
你能跟我来 是因为这里原本没有危险
You are only here because this was supposed to be no risk.
明白了吗？
Got it?
阿尔茜呼叫D小队 请提供会合坐标 听到没有？
Arcee to Delta Team, requesting rendezvous coordinates, do you copy?
阿尔茜 你又迷路了？
Arcee, you lost again?
你的方向传感器可以大修了
Your sensor-direction could use some improvement.
你的瞄准镜也该修了 挡板
So did your aim, Tailgate.
如果你在炮兵仓库干掉了那个狙击手
If you tagged that sniper back at the artillery depot
我就不必脱离大部队 跟敌人近身肉搏了
I wouldn't have to break rank and engage the enemy hand to hand.
听周围的声音 你大概是打赢了吧？
From the sound of things, I'm guessing you came out ahead?
这次你要是乖乖等着我 我就一五一十讲给你听
Try waiting up for me this time and I'll give you the blow-by-blow.
你的方位是？
What's your position?
仓库正北方 大约半分钟路程处（1klik＝72秒）
About half a klik from depot due north.
你能找到吧 搭档？
Think you can find it, partner?
相信我 挡板 我的探路能力…
Trust me, Tailgate. My navigation ability... Uh... Ah...
一个小建议…
Piece of advice...
把这里当成自己家吧
make yourself comfortable.
你得在这儿长住了
You are going to be here a while.
造访以来首次出手…
My first local...
该让人类尝尝我的毒刺了
Time for human kind to feel my sting.
阿尔茜 宇宙真小啊
Ar-cee, small universe.
小得出奇 毒蜘蛛
Too small, Airachnid.
你还在耿耿于怀？
You are still holding a grudge?
大战已经结束好几兆周期了
The war's been over for mega-cycles.
这话去跟霸天虎说吧
Tell that to the Decepticons.
最近我一直孤身旅行 追求我的新兴趣
These days I travel solo, in pursuit of my new hobby.
我看过你那箱纪念品了
I got a look at your souvenir case.
我把那叫做战利品
You mean my trophies.
我收藏濒危物种
I collect endangered species.
当然 他们并非真的濒危 只是因为遇到了我
Of course, they aren't really in danger, until they meet me.
我给人类也留了一个位置
And I have a slot reserved for human.
不必了！
Not gonna happen.
阿尔茜？
Arcee?
我说过让你等我！
I told you to wait for me!
那个 身为搭档 要同甘共苦
Well, partners don't ditch partners.
给我记住了：
Get this through your head:
你不是我的搭档 只是个累赘
You are not my partner, you are a liability.
我不信
I don't believe you.
从你的眼神能看出来 你害怕了 阿尔茜
I can see it in your eyes. You are afraid, Arcee
以前你从没怕过
and you're never afraid.
知道吗 作为汽车人来说 你的适应力非常强
You know, for an Autobot, your resilience is quite impressive.
事实上 我估计不管对你如何用刑
In fact, I'm guessing that no matter what I do to you
你都不会屈服
you'll never crack.
我说得对吗？
Am I right?
如我所料
That's what I thought.
挡板？
Tailgate?
你们对他做了什么？
What have you done to him?
没什么
Not much
暂时的
yet.
把我想知道的东西告诉我
Just tell me what I want to know
否则 哦 你是个聪明人
or, well, you're a smart bot.
你应该能想得出 挡板会遭什么罪吧？
I think you can imagine what happens to Tailgate next.
我不知道攻击地点
I don't know the attack coordinates.
我对火种源发誓 我说的是真的！
I swear upon the Allspark, it's the truth!
我们走着瞧
We shall see.
不 求求你！
No, please!
挡板！
Tailgate!
你说得对 杰克 我怕了
You are right, Jack, I am afraid
怕失去你！
of losing you.
你显然不善于和搭档相处 不是吗？
You sure have trouble hanging on to your partners, don't you?
挡板的下场 我们都知道
We both know what happened to Tailgate
不过 最近我偶然听到霸天虎们聊天
but I recently picked up some Decepticon radio chatter regarding the passing of Cliffjumper.
他们说飞过山死得很惨
有时候 你真该问问你自己 阿尔茜
At some point, you really have to ask yourself, Arcee.
问题到底在他们 还是在你自己？
Is it them, or is it me?
现在你明白了 杰克？
Do you get it now, Jack?
她不是冲我来的 她要猎杀本土物种
She is not interested in me. She hunts indigenous species
在地球上 那就意味着人类 你！
and she's on earth. That means humans. You!
快逃！
Run!
哈哈哈…这就是我喜欢单干的原因
Hahahaha... And that's why I now prefer to work alone.
看着你最亲近的人遭到不幸 真是太难过了
It's so sad when bad things happen to those close to you.
不过别误会
But don't get me wrong.
我十分期待着掐灭你的火种
I fully intend to snuff out your spark.
相信我 那会非常痛苦
And believe me, I will make it hurt.
不过 还有一件让你痛不欲生的事情
But that won't compare to the pain you feel knowing
我要把你的人类搭档加入我的收藏
I'm adding your human to my collection.
杰克！！
Jaaaaack!
精神可嘉 杰克 想玩矜持是吗
That's the spirit, Jack. Play hard to get.
我救不了他 我救不了我的搭档！
I couldn't save him. I couldn't save my partner!
杰克 对不起
Jack, I'm sorry.
我不该畏首畏尾…
I never should have looked back...
我应该…勇往直前
I should have... kept driving.
你好啊 杰克
Hello, Jack.
别自欺欺人了
Who am I kidding?
你把难度降得太低了 杰克
You're making this too easy, Jack
我不喜欢如此乏味
and I do not enjoy being bored.
好了 你逃到哪儿去了？
Now, where did you scamper off to?
如果想四处转转 杰克 跟我说就行了
If you wanted a tour, Jack, all you had to do was ask.
你看到那个空位了吗？
Did you spot the empty space?
但愿你喜欢
I hope you like it.
那儿很快就要挂上你的头了
It's where you'll soon hang your head.
能量
Energon.
杰克？
Jack?
杰克！
Jack!
杰克
Jack.
你没事吧？
Are you OK?
当然没事 我有求生包！
Yea, of course. Survival kit!
毒蜘蛛！
Airachnid!
唔…到此为止
Uh... so much for closure.
现在 毒蜘蛛留在地球上了
Now Airachnid's stuck here on Earth.
这大概不是什么好事
I'm not sure that's such a good thing.
我…很抱歉 今天让你面对那个疯子
I'm sorry you had to face that dement today.
你表现得很勇敢 杰克
You were pretty fearless there, Jack.
唉 其实我很害怕
Hgh... actually I was terrified.
主要是怕失去你
Mostly for you.
救护车 请求接通环陆桥
Ratchet, requesting Ground Bridge.
得让我的搭档离那些大虫子远点儿
Need to get my partner far away from any over-sized insects.
搭档 嗯哼？
Partner, Ughr?
小搭档 你还是得听我的
Junior partner. I can still pull rank.